[
    [
        {
            "id": "0",
            "level": "1",
            "question": "Which month is Sukkos in?",
            "choices": [
                "Elul",
                "Nissan",
                "Tishrei",
                "Adar"
            ],
            "answer": "Tishrei"
        },
        {
            "id": "1",
            "level": "1",
            "question": "How many Hakafos are there on Simchas Torah?",
            "choices": [
                "17",
                "7",
                "1",
                "8"
            ],
            "answer": "7"
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "id": "2",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "What day of Tishrei is Yom Kippur?",
            "choices": [
                "25",
                "15",
                "1",
                "10"
            ],
            "answer": "10"
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of the 5 forbidden pleasures on Yom Kippur ?",
            "choices": [
                "relaxing",
                "smearing",
                "drinking",
                "washing"
            ],
            "answer": "relaxing"
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "Who composed the Brachos of Shmona Esrei ?",
            "choices": [
                "Moshe Rabeinu",
                "Avraham Avinu",
                "The Anshei Kneses Hagedola",
                "The Rambam"
            ],
            "answer": "The Anshei Kneses Hagedola"
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "Who composed the Bracha of Al Netilas Lulav?",
            "choices": [
                "Moshe Rabeinu",
                "The Anshei Kneses Hagedola",
                "Avraham Avinu",
                "The Rambam"
            ],
            "answer": "The Anshei Kneses Hagedola"
        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "Which Shevet do Kohanim come from?",
            "choices": [
                "Levi",
                "Reuvain",
                "Aharon Hakohein",
                "Yehuda"
            ],
            "answer": "Levi"
        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "level": "2",
            "question": "How many days of Sefiras Haomer are there?",
            "choices": [
                "50",
                "40",
                "49",
                "60"
            ],
            "answer": "49"
        }
    ],
    [
        {
            "id": "7",
            "level": "3",
            "question": "Which of these brachos are Min Hatorah?",
            "choices": [
                "Shecheyanu",
                "Asher Yatzar",
                "Borei Nafashos",
                "Birchas Hamazon"
            ],
            "answer": "Birchas Hamazon"
        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "level": "3",
            "question": "Who wrote Talmud Bavli?",
            "choices": [
                "Rav and Shmuel",
                "Ravina and Rav Ashi",
                "Abaya and Rava",
                "Hillel and Shamai"
            ],
            "answer": "Ravina and Rav Ashi"
        }
    ]
]